ultimatehandyman.co.uk 2013-04-07

# Ultimate Handyman:privacy policy

Ultimate Handyman Privacy Policy

The Ultimate handyman privacy policy covers the following sites-

| www.ultimatehandyman.co.uk | www.ultimatehandyman.org | directory.ultimatehandyman.co.uk  
---|---|---  

**_Introduction_**

This site is governed by all the rules and regulation of the country of the United Kingdom and is hosted in the United Kingdom. The sites- www.ultimatehandyman.co.uk - www.ultimatehandyman.org and directory.ultimatehandyman.co.uk are owned and maintained by ultimate handyman limited (company number 5856701) and any enquires regarding privacy should in the first instance be directed to info@ultimatehandyman.co.uk  
Please note we hold all data for the minimum period of time prescribed by law for our country of origin any personal data that is held in a public facing part of the site can be removed if request in writing is made to the address below, please note a small administration charge may be applied. 

**_Tracking of data_**

This site tracks data in accordance with laws of United Kingdom  this site collects logs which include IP address but does not collect personally identifiable data from visitors without seeking their consent in the form of registration, the server logs are used to track problems within the site however the information is made available to police and other authorities in the host country ( United Kingdom) as dictated by local laws.  

**_3rd Party information_ **

While we do not sell information to third parties, we do pass information on to other parties to provide a richer experience the following third parties have access to some or all of our data.

Google Analytics cookies, Google analytics is our primary web statistics software no identifiable data is sent to Google analytics but rough geographic locations are included where available. 

**Google Advertising**

  * Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site/s. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to these sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html). 

**Forum Competition**

The winners of the forum competition are required to give their postal address so that the prize can be posted to the winners address. This address is only stored until the recipient confirms that the prize has been received and then the address is deleted. This address will never be passed on to another third party, unless the prize is being supplied by a third party.   

**_Cookies & Sessions - For tracking_**

These sites use cookies and sessions for tracking identifiable data about a machine this can include browser type amongst other information, however only personal identifiable information that you give can be placed in the cookie, the cookie resides in the machine that visited the site for a period of time. Our forum software tracks user actions anonymously and places a cookie to allow personalised services for those who have chosen to register and opt into the site. The arcade software also uses cookies to allow personalised services for those that have registered and sign into the arcade.   

_**Disputes**_

If you require information or believe an error has been made within this document you should in the first instance contact **info@ultimatehandyman.co.uk** or via a letter to-

Ultimate Handyman Limited

10 Borough Road  
Darwen  
Lancashire  
BB3 1PL 

_**Address**_

If you feel the matter has not be dealt with correctly you can contact the **[Information Commissioner's Office](http://www.ico.gov.uk/)**

We take your privacy seriously and do not sell or use your data in a way that could be considered inappropriate both morally and in the eyes of the governing laws.
